egifter.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy | eGifter

**eGifter Privacy Policy**

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information ("Information") by GroupGifting.com, Inc. d/b/a eGifter ("eGifter" or "We") in connection with the operation of the Web site located at [ http://www.eGifter.com](http://www.egifter.com/) and other Web sites it operates (each a "Site", and collectively known as the "Service") and supersedes any previous statement of such policies.  We take our obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and want to ensure users are fully informed about the Information they are providing to us.

Collection of Information.

In connection with the Service, we may collect Information in the following ways:

  * Through forms filled out by a User on one or more of the Sites
  * Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs
  * Via e-mail and other communications between a user and a Site
  * Through the use of third-party databases from which user Information is extracted and combined with Information obtained through other means.
  * Through any surveys or other marketing questionnaires that we use for research purposes.
  * All Information provided including pictures, videos, biography and any other Information that you provide voluntarily when organizing or participating in a Group Gift.

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information from users via "cookies" (small text files placed on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means.  We use cookies to save you time while using the Service, tell us who you are, track and target your interests in order to provide a better User experience.  Such information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties.    

_Please note that cookies are widely used by many reputable companies in order to make Web sites work more efficiently, as well as to provide information about the Service as well as enhancing a personalized experience.   We believe they are critical in providing you the best user experience._

To the extent third parties may place advertising on one or more of the Sites, such third parties may utilize cookies or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information.  We are not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which a Site is linked.

Types of Information Collected.

The following types of Information about a user are among those that may be collected in connection with the Service:  Name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, cell phone number, IP address, date of birth, age, gender, payment information, social media account information, referring site, and other technical information collected by a Site's servers. 

Collection of Information from Children.

The Sites are intended for users 18 years of age and over.  We do not knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with a Site from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.

Use of Information.

We may use Information collected in connection with the Service in the following ways:

  * To provide requested information, products and services to users via a Site or through other online or offline channels 
  * To improve the user experience with the Sites
  * In connection with the operation of the Sites
  * For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by the Service as well as selected third parties. 
  * For fraud prevention purposes.

In order to do the foregoing, we may provide the Information to trusted third parties, including but not limited to selected third party marketers as well as third party contractors providing services such as the operation of the Sites, communication services, and information verification.  We will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the specific uses set forth above. We may also provide Information to other Web sites we operate, and/or other business units within or to our affiliated entities.  We utilize electronic and physical security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage, but cannot guarantee the security or integrity of the Information and shall have no liability for breaches of security or integrity or third-party interception in transit. eGifter does not endorse, nor is eGifter responsible for the marketing of any third parties with which eGifter shares personally identifiable information. The entities with which eGifter shares personally identifying information are independent third parties and are not affiliated with eGifter. 

We may also disclose Information when it determines it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations, in connection with a merger, acquisition, asset purchase or sale of or by eGifter, or to protect our interests or safety, our customers, or other visitors to the Sites.

Opting Out from Offers.

At any time, a user may opt out from having the user's Information transferred by eGifter to third parties for use in such third parties' direct marketing efforts by sending a request to **[unsubscribe@egifter.com](mailto:unsubscribe@egifter.com)**. Such opting out may not apply to any communications from third parties to whom we may have provided Information regarding the user. Additionally,  a user may opt out from receiving future offers by following the opt-out instruction contained within each marketing message.Third parties' use of the Information is subject to such parties' own privacy policies, for which we shall not be responsible.

 Wireless Policy.

Pursuant to the above, we may use Information to provide the services requested by you, including utilizing a provided cell phone number for voice communication with you and services that display customized content and advertising via SMS messages sent to such provided cell phone number. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending an email to **[info@egifter.com](mailto:info@egifter.com).**

All standard messaging charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis.

Access to Information.

All users who provide their Information to the Site may modify and correct such Information by accessing their profiles within the Control Center.

Your California Privacy Rights.   
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Site who are California residents to request certain information regarding eGifter's disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to eGifter, Inc. 315 Main Street 2nd Floor, Huntington, NY 11743 **.**

Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Sites, and will apply to all information collected by us both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information.
